ELLI RAYNAI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 647 996 7420

elli@elliraynai.com

636 Danforth Ave, Toronto, M4K1R3

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/

<u>elliraynai.com</u>

github.com/eraynai

PROFILE

I am a full stack developer with a background in user experience design. My coding journey began with building interactive and engaging experiences in VR/AR. From there I began experimenting with the web, and fell in love with development. I have a passion for building applications and working collaboratively in a team to make the best possible product.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

React

Express

NodeJS

MongoDB

Vue

Django

PostgreSQL

Python

HTML

CSS Git

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly

May 2021 - August 2021

Interaction Design and Development George Brown College

September 2018 - April 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Technologist Intern

No Fixed Address | January 2021 - April 2021

- Sole frontend developer on a campaign for a client utilizing the Vue.js framework
- Consistently performed well under pressure amid tight time constraints and had to learn new development skills during the project
- Conducted market research on different types of technologies that could be utilized by clients

AR Designer

Snap | October 2020 - December 2020

- Participated in the Snap AR residency based on the my pitch for a machine learning experience called 'Nourish'
- Responsible for creative direction, user flows, concept designs, motion capture animation for 3D models, and programming interactions in JavaScript

Interaction Designer

Cream Productions | May 2020 - August 2020

Avoid using "I," "and," "the," and the use of any pronouns and prepositions. Whenever possible, quantify your accomplishments and responsibilities. That is, use numbers, amounts, dollar values, and percentages.

- · Designed and delivered a coherent vision for a casual VR game
- Conducted user interviews, competitive landscape analysis, and personas
- Built the game storyline, mechanics, and level design in collaboration with the development team

Interaction Designer

CFC Media Lab | February 2018 - June 2019

- Co-wrote, co-produced, and co-directed mixed media VR documentary
- Managed team of developers and designers to deliver the artistic vision of the piece
- Designed interactions, spatial sound design, shot volumetric capture of subjects, and edited the video of the subjects